{
    "subject": "resource/The_Chinese_University_of_Hong_Kong,_Shenzhen",
    "predicate": "ontology/vicePresident",
    "object": "resource/Tom_Z.Q._Luo",
    "human_readable": "Tom Z. Q. Luo is the vice president of The Chinese University of Hong Kong, Shenzhen.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9799062609672546,
            "question": "Who is the vice president of The Chinese University of Hong Kong, Shenzhen?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9795960187911987,
            "question": "Name the university where Tom Z. Q. Luo serves as vice president."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9733818769454956,
            "question": "What is the full name of the vice president of The Chinese University of Hong Kong, Shenzhen?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9520344734191895,
            "question": "Is Tom Z. Q. Luo associated with a university in Hong Kong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9507270455360413,
            "question": "What position does Tom Z. Q. Luo hold at The Chinese University of Hong Kong, Shenzhen?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8059207201004028,
            "question": "Is The Chinese University of Hong Kong, Shenzhen a well-known institution?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7321938276290894,
            "question": "Where is The Chinese University of Hong Kong, Shenzhen located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7209416627883911,
            "question": "What is the name of the university that Tom Z. Q. Luo is affiliated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5415262579917908,
            "question": "Can you provide more information about Tom Z. Q. Luo's background and accomplishments?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.516949474811554,
            "question": "Does Tom Z. Q. Luo have a leadership role in an educational institution?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Tom Z. Q. Luo is the vice president of The Chinese University of Hong Kong, Shenzhen.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4388_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you provide more information about Tom Z. Q. Luo's background and accomplishments?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4388_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the university that Tom Z. Q. Luo is affiliated with?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4388_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where is The Chinese University of Hong Kong, Shenzhen located?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4388_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4388_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4388_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4388_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4388_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4388_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4388_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4388_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4388_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4388_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4388_85.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response to your query:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple pieces of information that confirm Tom Z.Q. Luo's position as Vice President (Academic) and Director of various institutions at The Chinese University of Hong Kong, Shenzhen."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis response indicates that according to the provided documents, Professor Tom Z.Q. Luo is indeed listed as the Vice President (Academic) of The Chinese University of Hong Kong, Shenzhen."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}